tellapart.com 2017-09-20

# TellApart Privacy Policy

#### **This Privacy Policy was last updated on August 15, 2016.**

TellApart Inc. (“TellApart”) provides businesses (“Business Partners”), including e-commerce sites and advertisers, access to a set of technologies and processes designed to display advertisements to consumers (the “TellApart Ads”).

This Privacy Policy describes TellApart’s privacy practices as they pertain to (i) visitors to our website located at www.TellApart.com (our “Site”), and (ii) our targeted advertising technology service (“Technology”).

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us at [tellapartprivacy@twitter.com](mailto:tellapartprivacy@twitter.com).

### 1\. Site — Information Collection and Use

The Site is intended primarily to offer information about TellApart and the services we provide.

**Information Collected via the Site**

We collect Personally Identifiable Information (“PII”) from the Site when you choose to provide it to us. PII is information that can be used to identify a particular person or entity. This includes, but is not limited to: full name, postal address, telephone number, or email address. For example, you may choose to send us PII about yourself in an email or by completing an online form on this Site. We use this information only to contact you to respond to your inquiry. We also collect Non-Personally Identifiable Information (Non-PII) via the Site. Non-PII may include your IP address, pages viewed on this Site, browser type, user agent, Internet Service Provider, the time/date of your visit to this Site, and your computer’s operating system (e.g., Windows XP).

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

We use “cookies” and other technology to help us manage this Site. Cookies are small text files that contain a string of alphanumeric characters. We also use persistent cookies on this Site in order to help us manage the opt-out process for our Technology. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You may be able to remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser’s “help” file. For more information about cookies please visit <http://www.allaboutcookies.org/cookies/>.

**Third Party Websites**

The Site may contain links to other websites. Such websites may use cookies and/or other data collection tools. TellApart is not responsible for the privacy practices, policies or content of such other websites. TellApart encourages everyone to read the posted privacy policies whenever interacting with any website to learn more about the privacy practices of that website. TellApart has no control over the use of information by third party websites, and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose any information to those websites.

### 2\. TellApart Technology — Information Collection and Use

**Overview of TellApart’s Technology and Data Collection**

Our Technology collects information about the website(s) and mobile application(s) that you visit and the advertisements that you see while online. Using our technology, we may collect data about you in the following contexts: when TellApart or one of our Business Partners purchase online advertisements on a website or mobile application that you visit (“Advertising Data”); and/or when one of our Business Partners or advertising technology partners uses our Technology on a website or mobile application that you visit (“Business Partner Data”). The type of Advertising Data we collect includes the number of advertisement requests received, the number of advertisements you are shown, the identity of the website or mobile application you are visiting and the number of clicks you may make on a particular advertisement, but in all cases Advertising Data is Non-PII. The type of Business Partner Data we collect includes information regarding the pages and products you have viewed, the identity of products purchased, the time you spend on particular parts of the site or app and product price. Business Partner Data may in some cases include PII. However, we do not associate this information with the information that is separately gathered off the Business Partners’ websites and mobile applications through our online advertising activities.

We use the information collected by our Technology in order to help make the TellApart Ads you see on this browser or device, and other browsers or devices that we think are associated with this browser or device, more relevant to you, to improve our Technology, and for ad delivery and measurement purposes. We also may disclose Non-PII to our Business Partners in connection with the provision of TellApart Technology services.

**Cookies, JavaScript and Web Beacons, and Other Technologies**

TellApart uses cookies and other technologies in connection with our Technology and our collection of both Advertising Data and Business Partner Data. These types of technologies help TellApart better understand the effectiveness of a TellApart Ad (for example, by tracking the way in which you may respond to, select and interact with a TellApart Ad or any content provided therein, or the location and context in which you view a TellApart Ad). TellApart’s technology also helps control the number of times you view a TellApart Ad. Although most web browsers automatically accept cookies, some browsers’ settings can be modified to decline cookies or alert you when a website is attempting to place a cookie on your computer. Consult the help manual for your browser for detailed information. If you do not accept cookies, however, you may not be able to enjoy the full functionality of many of the websites you visit.

TellApart also uses JavaScript and web beacons, in combination with cookies, to analyze usage patterns. The use of these technologies allows TellApart to record that someone has visited a particular webpage, along with additional Non-PII that the website may choose to include with the beacon.

**Information Received from Other Third Parties**

In some cases, we may choose to work with third party data providers to support requirements that may arise from our Business Partners. For example, these providers may use our technology to combine anonymous third party data with the data collected by our technology in order to further tailor advertising content to their customers. In conjunction with information collected using our Technology, we use this information in order to help make the TellApart Ads you see more relevant to you, to improve our Technology, and for ad delivery, measurement and reporting purposes.

**Third Party Links and Websites**

TellApart Ads may contain links to other websites, including those of our Business Partners. Such websites may use cookies and/or other data collection tools. TellApart is not responsible for the privacy practices, policies or the content of such websites. TellApart encourages everyone to read the posted privacy policies when interacting with any website to learn more about the privacy practices of that website. TellApart has no control over the use of any information by third party websites, and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose any information. Similarly, TellApart does not have access to, or control of, the cookies and/or other data collection tools that may be placed on any advertisement by a third-party, including those of our Business Partners, and this Privacy Policy does not cover the use of cookies and/or other data collection tools by any third party.

### 3\. Our Disclosure of Information About You

TellApart is not in the business of selling your information. We consider this information to be a vital part of our relationship with you. There are, however, certain circumstances in which we may share information about you with certain third parties without further notice to you, as set forth below:

**Business Transfers and Affiliates** :

As we develop our business, we might sell or buy businesses or assets. In the event of a corporate sale, merger, reorganization, dissolution or similar event, information about you may be part of the transferred assets. We may also disclose information about you within our corporate family, including to our parent company, Twitter, Inc. You acknowledge and agree that any such recipient of information about you will have the right to use that information as disclosed herein.

**Agents, Consultants, Service Providers and Related Third Parties** :

TellApart, like many businesses, sometimes hires other companies to perform certain business-related functions. Examples of such functions include maintaining databases, hosting services and the like. When we employ another company to perform a function of this nature, we only provide them with the information that they need to perform their specific function.

**Legal Requirements** :

TellApart may disclose information about you if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to (i) comply with a legal obligation, (ii) protect and defend the rights or property of TellApart or others, (iii) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of our users or the public, or (iv) protect against legal liability.

### 4\. Information Security

The security of your information is important to us. We have implemented reasonable security measures to protect the information in our care, both during transmission and once we receive it. This includes, but is not limited to the use of encryption. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your information, we cannot guarantee its security.

If you have any questions about our security practices, please send an email to us at [tellapartprivacy@twitter.com](mailto:tellapartprivacy@twitter.com).

### 5\. Opt-out of Interest-Based Advertising

**On the web:**

You may opt out of receiving TellApart’s interest-based advertising on this browser by clicking on the link below:

Kindly note that when you opt out, TellApart records that choice in your browser cookies. If after opting out, you delete, block or otherwise restrict cookies, or if you use a different computer or Internet browser, then your browser will no longer have a record of your opt­-out status and you will need to renew your opt-out choice for that browser.

**For mobile applications:**

Your iOS device may provide a “Limit Ad Tracking” setting. On Android devices, your settings may allow you to “Opt out of Interest-Based Ads.” When you have opted out using one of these settings, TellApart will neither (1) use in-app information collected from that device to infer your interests nor (2) serve ads to that device that are targeted based on your inferred interests.

If you have any questions about these opt-­out mechanisms, please feel free to contact us at **tellapartprivacy@twitter.com**. Please note that while opting out limits TellApart’s collection of information to serve ads based on your inferred interests as well as your receipt of interest-based ads from TellApart, it does not prevent you from receiving targeted ads from MoPub, Twitter, or other third parties. Also note that you may continue to receive contextual ads from TellApart after opting out.

To opt out of the interest-based advertising delivered by other NAI member companies please [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/).

### 6\. General Information

When working with sites whose product catalog includes personal care items, we do not have access to your medical information but may on occasion display advertisements for non-sensitive products such as soap, clothing and toys for infants.

**Network Advertising Initiative**

TellApart is a member of the Network Advertising Initiative and adheres to the Network Advertising Initiative Standards ([NAI Code of Conduct](http://www.google.com/url?q=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.networkadvertising.org%2F2013_Principles.pdf&sa=D&sntz=1&usg=AFQjCNGHjVygQJagJTkqmavGo31s7DecGg), [Mobile Application Code](http://www.networkadvertising.org/mobile/NAI_Mobile_Application_Code.pdf)). The NAI offers an online web [opt-out](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/) platform to allow consumers to express their choices and provides general information related to privacy and [Interest Based Advertising](http://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising).

**Digital Advertising Alliance**

TellApart adheres to the Digital Advertising Alliance Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising. You can opt out of interest-based advertising from TellApart and many other companies by visiting the Digital Advertising Alliance’s [ Consumer Choice page](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/).

**Data Retention**

Non-PII data related to online behavioral advertising is stored with the TellApart cookie and is deleted when the cookie expires, which is currently set to two years from the last time you have visited a TellApart business partner.

**Information Relating to Children**

Our products and services are designed for those 13 years of age and older. We do not knowingly collect PII from anyone under the age of 13. If we are made aware that we have received PII from someone under 13, we will use reasonable efforts to remove that information from our records.

**Updating your PII**

If you would like us to update, correct or delete any PII about you that we may possess, please send us an email at [tellapartprivacy@twitter.com](mailto:tellapartprivacy@twitter.com) and we will process your request within a reasonable period of time after receipt.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

This privacy policy is subject to change. If we make any material or substantive changes in the way that we use the PII collected through this Website, we will post notice of those changes on the Website and in this privacy policy.

**Contact Information**

For questions or concerns relating to privacy, please send us an email at [tellapartprivacy@twitter.com](mailto:tellapartprivacy@twitter.com).
